[Dreams]
[꿈]
Will the article be published?
기사가 나올까요?
No, I've resolved the issue.
아니요, 문제를 해결했습니다.
But how?
하지만 어떻게?
GM?
GM?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Please don't be so nervous, President Makita.
너무 긴장하지 마세요, 마키타 회장님.
I've brought you good news.
좋은 소식을 가져왔습니다.
What is it?
그것은 무엇입니까?
General Manager Sakurazaki will be dismissed by month's end.
총지배인 사쿠라자키 월말까지 해고됩니다.
Therefore, President Makita.
그러니까 마키타 사장.
I ask that you be our interim GM.
임시 GM이 되어 주시기 바랍니다.
Was it to retract the article about your brother?
기사를 철회하기 위한 것이었나요? 네 동생에 대해서?
I've put together a plan and materials for the future.
I've put together a plan 그리고 미래를 위한 소재.
Why are you agreeing to this?
왜 이것에 동의합니까?
GM!
GM!
I always assumed the Dreams were a team of lazy individuals.
나는 항상 추측했다 Dreams는 게으른 개인들로 구성된 팀이었습니다.
But I was wrong.
그러나 나는 틀렸다.
You claw your way towards victory,
당신은 승리를 향해 나아가고 있습니다.
and remain positive in the face of adversity.
그리고 역경 속에서도 긍정적인 태도를 유지하세요.
President Makita.
마키타 회장.
I was glad to be proven wrong.
나는 틀렸다는 것이 입증되어 기뻤습니다.
I entrust the role of interim GM to you.
임시 GM의 역할을 당신에게 맡깁니다.
I can't.
나는 할 수 없다.
You are our shining hope.
당신은 우리의 빛나는 희망입니다.
This was an order from President Negishi.
이것은 네기시 사장의 명령이었다.
And...
그리고...
it is my final wish to the team.
그것이 팀에 대한 나의 마지막 소원이다.
That can't be true.
그것은 사실일 수 없습니다.
I know you want to win.
나는 당신이 이기고 싶어한다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
Are we not a team?
우리는 팀이 아니지?
Let's get through this, together.
함께 이겨냅시다.
GM!
GM!
I'm not the GM anymore.
나는 더 이상 GM이 아닙니다.
Why?
왜?
Why can't you ask for our help?
왜 우리에게 도움을 요청할 수 없나요?
Do you not trust us?
우리를 믿지 못하시나요?
I was guaranteed two years of my salary.
나는 2년 동안의 급여를 보장받았다.
So what?
그래서 뭐?
President Makita.
마키타 회장.
I have no attachment to the team.
나는 팀에 대한 애착이 없다.
Nor do I have any interest in baseball.
야구에도 전혀 관심이 없습니다.
I believe I've accomplished enough.
나는 충분히 성취했다고 믿는다.
Is that how you really feel?
정말 그런 기분인가요?
Do you truly feel well accomplished?
정말 성취감이 느껴지시나요?
Of course.
물론.
I understand.
이해합니다.
It's not just the Dreams who need to change.
변화가 필요한 것은 Dreams만이 아닙니다.
You need to change yourself as well.
자신도 변화해야 합니다.
Thank you for everything.
모든 것에 감사드립니다.
Your renowned colleague, Mr. Sakurazaki,
당신의 유명한 동료인 사쿠라자키 씨
will be leaving at the end of this month.
이번 달 말에 떠날 거예요.
What happened?
무슨 일이에요?
He chose to step down of his own accord.
그는 스스로 사임을 선택했습니다.
The GM negotiated unfairly with our catcher.
GM은 우리 포수와 부당한 협상을 벌였습니다.
He damaged the team's image.
그는 팀의 이미지를 손상시켰습니다.
He even took advantage of his position to hire his brother.
심지어 그는 자신의 지위를 이용했다. 그의 동생을 고용하기 위해.
I believe his dismissal is entirely deserved.
나는 그의 해고가 전적으로 정당하다고 생각합니다.
Please strive to fill the void left by Mr. Sakurazaki.
공백을 메우기 위해 노력해주세요 사쿠라자키 씨가 남긴 것입니다.
Woah, woah, woah!
와, 와, 와!
Let go of me!
날 놔줘!
There wasn't any foul play to speak of!
말할 수 있는 반칙은 없었습니다!
I understand, but not now.
이해합니다만 지금은 아닙니다.
If we don't speak up, the GM will be...
우리가 말하지 않으면 GM은...
We will continue to support the Dreams in their endeavors.
앞으로도 드림즈를 응원하겠습니다 그들의 노력에.
Have I made myself clear?
나는 내 자신을 분명히 했는가?
To survive in an organization,
조직에서 살아남으려면
no one can stick to their beliefs.
누구도 자신의 신념을 고수할 수 없습니다.
I wish you all the best, Interim GM.
임시 GM님, 최선을 다하시길 바랍니다.
Oh...
아...
Let me in on your secret plan, GM.
당신의 비밀 계획을 알려주세요, GM.
You'll come back with a real bang, right?
진짜 빵빵하게 돌아오겠죠?
Right?
오른쪽?
My salary has been guaranteed. I won't be coming back.
내 월급은 보장됐어요. 나는 돌아오지 않을 것이다.
You're only in it for the money?
당신은 단지 돈 때문에 거기에 있습니까?
Of course.
물론.
No, I don't believe it.
아니요, 믿을 수 없습니다.
You clearly have passion.
당신에겐 분명 열정이 있습니다.
Everyone here has been influenced by it.
여기 있는 모든 사람들이 그 영향을 받았습니다.
Hard work is rewarded, right? I learned that from you.
열심히 일한 만큼 보상을 받는 거죠, 그렇죠? 나는 당신에게서 그것을 배웠습니다.
I've never been rewarded.
저는 보상을 받은 적이 없습니다.
Not once.
한 번도 아닙니다.
You've led plenty of teams to victory!
당신은 수많은 팀을 승리로 이끌었습니다!
And they've all been disbanded.
그리고 그들은 모두 해체되었습니다.
I hurt the players' pride and destroyed the team.
선수들의 자존심을 상하게 했어요 그리고 팀을 무너뜨렸습니다.
If I were President Negishi,
내가 네기시 대통령이라면
I would consider firing the GM as well.
GM 해고도 고려해보겠습니다.
No, but...
아니, 하지만...
Hey.
여기요.
GM.
GM.
Hey!
여기요!
Thank you.
감사합니다.
I still believe in you, okay?
난 아직도 당신을 믿어요, 그렇죠?
Please publish the article as scheduled.
예정대로 기사를 게시해 주세요.
Yes. Of course.
예. 물론.
[Dreams GM, hired his jobless brother?] Seriously?
[드림스GM, 백수 동생 고용?] 진심으로요?
They published the article anyway!
어쨌든 그들은 기사를 출판했습니다!
What? What's wrong?
무엇? 무슨 일이야?
- See? - Unbelievable.
- 보다? - 말도 안 돼요.
What an absolute scumbag.
정말 쓰레기입니다.
Prez, could I have a minute?
프레즈, 잠시 시간 좀 가질 수 있을까요?
Shirasaki and Kato have requested to withdraw their contracts.
시라사키와 카토 계약 철회를 요청했습니다.
See? I knew it.
보다? 나는 그것을 알고 있었다.
They said they can't trust a negotiation
협상을 믿을 수 없다고 하더군요
given by an analyst we let in through connections.
분석가가 제공한 우리는 연결을 통해 들어옵니다.
They're quick.
그들은 빠릅니다.
I denied any foul play, but they wouldn't listen.
나는 어떤 반칙도 부인했다. 하지만 그들은 듣지 않았습니다.
I'm going to go renegotiate.
재협상하러 가겠습니다.
We're counting on you.
우리는 당신을 믿고 있습니다.
- Good luck. - Alright, it's a go! Go!
- 행운을 빌어요. - 좋아요, 이제 갑니다! 가다!
- Before I go. - What? What's wrong?
- 가기 전에요. - 무엇? 무슨 일이야?
Alright!
괜찮은!
Huzzah! Huzzah!
만세! 만세!
- Miyahara! - That's right!
- 미야하라! - 좋아요!
Go, go, Miyahara!
가, 가, 미야하라!
Are you really leaving the Dreams?
정말 드림즈를 떠나는 건가요?
If it's to protect me, don't.
나를 보호하기 위해서라면 그러지 마세요.
You don't need any more protecting.
더 이상 보호할 필요가 없습니다.
This is my problem to deal with.
이것이 내가 처리해야 할 문제이다.
You joined the Dreams fair and square.
Dreams Fair and Square에 참여하셨습니다.
All you have to do is prove yourself.
당신이 해야 할 일은 자신을 증명하는 것뿐입니다.
I know.
알아요.
But...
하지만...
Why are you always like this?
왜 항상 이런가요?
Are you sure, Jun?
정말인가요, Jun?
I no longer deserve to be happy.
나는 더 이상 행복할 자격이 없습니다.
You can't bear it anymore, can you?
더 이상 참을 수 없겠죠?
Dinner's ready. [Risa]
저녁 식사가 준비되었습니다. [리사]
Huh?
뭐?
Hey, aren't you going to eat?
야, 밥 안 먹을 거야?
I made omelette rice today.
오늘은 오믈렛밥을 만들었어요.
No, not hungry.
아니요, 배고프지 않아요.
Huh? Why?
뭐? 왜?
Oh no.
안 돼.
Did you get fired?
해고됐나요?
You're so insensitive.
당신은 너무 무감각합니다.
Our finances are in trouble. What should we do?
우리 재정이 곤경에 빠졌습니다. 우리는 무엇을 해야 합니까?
I'm not the one who got fired.
나는 해고된 사람이 아니다.
Oh, I see.
알겠어요.
So it was that guy. He got fired?
그러니까 그 사람이었어. 그 사람 해고됐어요?
Well, I worried for nothing.
글쎄, 나는 아무것도 걱정하지 않았다.
If you're so worried, get a job.
그렇게 걱정되면 취업하세요.
Come on, let's just eat.
자, 그냥 먹자.
Here, dinner's ready.
자, 저녁 식사 준비됐어요.
This is Makita, speaking.
저는 마키타입니다.
President Makita.
마키타 대통령.
Please let me handle the salary negotiations.
연봉 협상은 제가 처리하게 해주세요.
What?
무엇?
I'll re-explain our criteria to all players.
모든 플레이어에게 우리의 기준을 다시 설명하겠습니다.
You'll be at an intense disadvantage.
당신은 엄청난 불이익을 당하게 될 것입니다.
That's precisely why I wish to do this.
이것이 바로 제가 이 일을 하고 싶은 이유입니다.
For the sake of the team.
팀을 위해서.
And for my brother.
그리고 내 동생을 위해서.
I will officially explain the GM's scandal,
GM의 스캔들에 대해 공식적으로 설명하겠습니다,
and his dismissal early next week.
그리고 다음 주 초에 해고됩니다.
He will bear all the responsibility.
그 사람이 모든 책임을 지게 될 것이다.
And to free our poor, unfortunate players,
그리고 우리의 불쌍하고 불운한 플레이어들을 해방시키기 위해
I will announce the team be disbanded.
팀 해체를 발표하겠습니다.
Do you know what this is?
이게 뭔지 아세요?
A daifuku, I believe.
찹쌀떡이라고 생각합니다.
And what is it wrapped in?
그리고 그것은 무엇으로 포장되어 있습니까?
Mochi, sir.
모찌님.
Excellent. Yes, this is mochi.
훌륭한. 네, 이게 모찌입니다.
Give it a try.
한번 시도해 보세요.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
How is it? Good?
어때요? 좋은?
Yes. It's delicious.
예. 맛있어요.
Mochi is made to be a consumable object.
떡은 소모품으로 만들어졌습니다.
I have no need for empty promises of mochi.
떡에 대한 공허한 약속은 필요 없습니다.
Do you understand?
이해했나요?
Of...
...
Of course...
물론이죠...
Of course, sir.
물론이죠, 선생님.
You joking around?
농담하는 거야?
I would never.
나는 결코 그렇게 하지 않을 것이다.
Make sure you get me some delicious mochi.
맛있는 떡을 꼭 사주세요.
Don't you dare fail.
감히 실패하지 마십시오.
Understood.
이해했다.
It's fine. My salary will be in the hundred millions.
괜찮습니다. 내 월급 수억에 달할 것이다.
Go on and buy big.
가서 크게 사세요.
Yeah, later.
응, 나중에.
Hello?
안녕하세요?
Yeah, I'm headed home now.
응, 나 지금 집에 가는 중이야.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
If you're hurting, tell me.
아프면 말해주세요.
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
I know...
알아요...
I'm causing you trouble.
내가 당신을 곤란하게 만들고 있어요.
I know that, but...
그건 알지만...
I just, I want to...
난 그냥, 난...
No, never mind.
아뇨, 신경 쓰지 마세요.
I'll buy us some meat on the way home.
집에 가는 길에 고기 좀 사올게요.
Talk to you soon.
곧 얘기해 보세요.
I knew I'd find you here.
나는 당신을 여기서 찾을 줄 알았습니다.
Akito contacted me.
Akito contacted me.
I was fired.
나는 해고되었습니다.
Akito filled me in.
아키토가 나를 채워줬어요.
Coming here won't bring any of it back.
여기 와도 아무것도 가져오지 못할 거야.
Not her.
그녀는 아닙니다.
Not us.
우리는 아닙니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
Oh, stop it.
아, 그만해요.
I've seen enough of you blaming yourself.
나는 당신이 자신을 비난하는 것을 충분히 보았습니다.
It's time we both move on.
이제 우리 둘 다 나아갈 시간입니다.
This is not where you belong right now.
지금은 이곳이 당신이 속한 곳이 아닙니다.
You can't win baseball on your own.
야구는 혼자서는 이길 수 없다.
What matters is the team, right?
중요한 건 팀이겠죠?
Teams are where you share clashing opinions.
팀은 상충되는 의견을 공유하는 곳입니다.
Where you can be true to yourself.
자신에게 솔직해질 수 있는 곳.
Where you can share both joys and sorrows.
기쁨과 슬픔을 함께 나눌 수 있는 곳.
I know you want to protect that team.
나는 당신이 그 팀을 보호하고 싶어한다는 것을 알고 있습니다.
But the team wants to protect you, too.
하지만 팀도 당신을 보호하고 싶어합니다.
What? Did I say something strange?
무엇? 내가 뭔가 이상한 말을 했나?
No.
아니요.
You know nothing about baseball, do you?
야구에 대해 아무것도 모르시죠?
Hey!
여기요!
This is what sports are all about.
이것이 스포츠의 전부입니다.
Am I wrong?
내가 틀렸나요?
Thank you.
감사합니다.
If it's not a fair assessment, we have no intention of signing.
공정한 평가가 아니라면 우리는 서명할 생각이 없습니다.
Our assessment is entirely fair.
우리의 평가는 전적으로 공정합니다.
You let a complete amateur do the work.
완전한 아마추어에게 작업을 맡기면 됩니다.
You're practically scamming us.
당신은 사실상 우리에게 사기를 치는 셈입니다.
He was not hired through connections.
그는 인맥을 통해 고용되지 않았습니다.
We determined he was an irreplaceable asset, and offered him the role.
우리는 그가 대체할 수 없는 자산이라고 판단했습니다. 그리고 그에게 역할을 제안했습니다.
My name is Akito Sakurazaki, of the Data Analytics Team.
내 이름은 사쿠라자키 아키토, 데이터분석팀입니다.
Please allow me to explain our criteria for this assessment.
설명할 수 있게 해주세요 이 평가에 대한 우리의 기준.
Hey, Iwata.
안녕, 이와타.
Leave the negotiations with the GM to me.
GM과의 협상은 나에게 맡겨주세요.
Let's go.
갑시다.
Right.
오른쪽.
First, I admit that your salaries are below the market average.
우선 연봉은 인정합니다 시장 평균보다 낮습니다.
See?
보다?
Our team's financial situation is to blame.
우리 팀의 재정 상황이 탓이다.
We're sorry we cannot do more.
더 이상 할 수 없어서 죄송합니다.
Are you kidding me?
농담하는 거야?
Don't think that's a valid excuse.
그것이 타당한 변명이라고 생각하지 마십시오.
Still, these contracts are favorable for you all.
그래도 이 계약은 당신 모두에게 유리합니다.
Huh?
뭐?
Mr. Shirasaki.
시라사키 씨.
Your batting average is a .214.
당신의 타율은 .214이다.
Your stolen base success rate is 50%.
기본 도난 성공률은 50%입니다.
These stats are comparable to batters in the minor leagues.
이 통계는 비교할 수 있습니다. 마이너리그의 타자들에게.
What?
무엇?
Why's everyone such a harsh critic?
왜 다들 이렇게 가혹한 비판을 하는 걸까요?
Mr. Shirasaki.
시라사키 씨.
There's more.
더 많은 것이 있습니다.
However, your batted balls have great velocity.
그러나 당신의 타구는 대단한 속도를 가지고 있습니다.
Your average batted velocity
당신의 평균 타구 속도
ranks within the top 15% of the entire league.
상위 15% 내 순위 리그 전체의.
If you continue to step up to plate,
계속해서 한 단계 더 발전한다면,
you could make a name for yourself as a home run hitter.
너는 너 자신의 이름을 알릴 수 있을 거야 홈런타자로서.
What? Is that a compliment?
무엇? 칭찬인가요?
You ought to offer me more!
나에게 더 많은 것을 제안해야합니다!
But this is only if you continue to bat.
하지만 이는 계속해서 타석을 치는 경우에만 해당됩니다.
Given your current stats,
현재 통계를 고려하면,
other teams would barely put you in play.
다른 팀에서는 당신을 거의 플레이하지 않을 것입니다.
But with Tatsuya Kudo gone,
하지만 쿠도 타츠야가 사라지자
the Dreams are short on home run hitters.
Dreams는 홈런 타자가 부족합니다.
You would play at least 100 games with us.
당신은 우리와 함께 적어도 100개의 게임을 할 것입니다.
That's about 4.37 times more often than if you played with another team.
약 4.37배 더 자주 발생합니다. 다른 팀에서 플레이하는 것보다요.
Yes, your salary next season will be low.
네, 다음 시즌 연봉은 낮을 겁니다.
But make a name for yourself next season,
하지만 다음 시즌에는 이름을 떨쳐보세요.
and a number of teams,
그리고 여러 팀,
including the Dreams, will be writing you offers.
드림즈를 비롯해 당신에게 제안을 쓸 것입니다.
Don't just look at the present.
현재만 보지 마세요.
Look towards the future,
미래를 바라보세요
and you'll realize this contract isn't such a bad deal.
그리고 넌 이 계약을 깨닫게 될 거야 그렇게 나쁜 거래는 아닙니다.
Do you still believe his assessment is the work of an amateur?
아직도 그의 평가를 믿나요? 아마추어 작품인가?
I thought I was meeting the GM today. What's going on?
오늘 GM을 만나는 줄 알았어요. 무슨 일이야?
I am the current acting GM.
저는 현재 GM 대리입니다.
So that amateur was fired after all.
그래서 그 아마추어는 결국 해고되었습니다.
Are the Dreams going to be okay?
드림즈는 괜찮을까요?
Don't be anxious.
걱정하지 마세요.
Likewise.
비슷하게.
I hear Shirasaki's crew rescinded their contracts?
시라사키의 크루가 들려요 계약을 취소했나요?
Not to worry. It's been taken care of.
걱정하지 마세요. 처리되었습니다.
That so.
그렇습니다.
Iwata is the only one left.
이와타만 남았다.
All I ask for is a fair evaluation.
내가 요구하는 것은 공정한 평가뿐이다.
And don't try offering him a meager 60 million again.
그리고 그에게 제안하려고 하지 마세요 다시 6 천만 달러가 부족합니다.
Of course. We have re-evaluated our negotiation.
물론. 우리는 협상을 재평가했습니다.
[74 million yen]
[7,400만엔]
Hey.
여기요.
Are you serious about signing with me?
나와 계약하는 것에 대해 진지하게 생각하시나요?
Given the average rate amongst other professionals,
평균 금리를 고려하면 다른 전문가들 사이에서는
our analyst has estimated your average salary to be
우리 분석가는 추정했습니다 당신의 평균 급여는
around 70 million yen this season.
이번 시즌에는 약 7천만 엔 정도입니다.
[League estimate: 70 million yen]
[리그 추정액: 7천만엔]
An assessment done by an amateur, I take it.
아마추어가 평가한 것으로 받아들입니다.
Are you aware of the blog, "Banzai Baseball"?
'만세야구' 블로그를 아시나요?
It's quite famous, and relied upon by many professional analysts.
꽤 유명해서 많이 의지하는 곳이에요 많은 전문 분석가에 의해.
It is also run by our new hire.
이곳도 신입 직원이 운영하고 있습니다.
This is the most accurate assessment a baseball analyst can offer.
가장 정확한 평가입니다 야구 분석가가 제안할 수 있습니다.
The most accurate assessment?
가장 정확한 평가는?
Now you're being ridiculous.
지금 당신은 우스꽝스럽습니다.
Offer me this little,
나에게 이 작은 것을 주세요
and I'm taking the next season off for rehab.
그리고 다음 시즌에는 재활을 위해 휴가를 낼 예정이에요.
Know what I'm getting at?
내가 무슨 말을 하는지 알아?
You'll be losing the catcher
너는 포수를 잃게 될 거야
who can make the most of Sawada's pitches.
사와다의 공을 최대한 활용할 수 있는 사람.
You'd be throwing away your chance to escape last place!
넌 기회를 버릴 거야 꼴찌를 탈출하기 위해!
I see.
알겠어요.
Does this mean you see potential in our next season?
이것이 의미하는 바는 무엇입니까? 다음 시즌에 잠재력이 보이나요?
So do I.
나도 마찬가지야.
I believe we can aim for victory next year.
내년에는 우승을 노릴 수 있을 거라 믿습니다.
If we get the whole team, that is.
팀 전체를 얻으면 그렇습니다.
Hey, now.
안녕, 지금.
Don't distract him with a dream.
꿈으로 그의 주의를 산만하게 하지 마십시오.
Professional baseball is a business. It's no after-school club.
프로야구는 사업이다. 방과후 클럽이 아닙니다.
If you want Iwata's power, then make him a reasonable offer.
이와타의 힘을 원한다면, 그런 다음 그에게 합리적인 제안을 하십시오.
That is why we're offering him the average 70 million,
그렇기 때문에 우리는 그에게 제안하는 것입니다. 평균 7천만 명,
with an additional 4 million to express our expectations for him.
400만 추가로 그에 대한 우리의 기대를 표현하기 위해.
Are you even listening to me?
당신도 내 말을 듣고 있나요?
I understand.
이해합니다.
Iwata is an indispensable player for the Dreams.
이와타는 빼놓을 수 없는 선수다. 꿈을 위해.
I will offer an additional 8 million, for an annual salary of 82 million yen.
추가로 800만원을 제시하겠습니다. 연봉 8200만엔.
[82 million yen]
[8,200만엔]
Raising someone's salary means lowering someone else's.
누군가의 월급을 올리다 다른 사람을 낮추는 것을 의미합니다.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
I know.
알고 있어요.
I'm causing you trouble.
내가 당신에게 문제를 일으키고 있어요.
That's why we negotiate with all our might every day.
그게 우리가 협상하는 이유야 매일 온 힘을 다해.
Still, we cannot give up on you, Iwata.
그래도 이와타 씨를 포기할 수는 없습니다.
Even if that means offering less to others.
비록 그것이 다른 사람들에게 더 적은 것을 제공한다는 것을 의미하더라도.
Then do just that.
그럼 그렇게 하세요.
Get him what he deserves!
그에게 마땅한 것을 가져다주세요!
Isn't that right?
그렇지 않나요?
I hope to be offered a fair price.
정당한 가격으로 제공되길 바랍니다.
Exactly.
정확히.
He's a candidate for next year's Gold Glove Award.
그 사람이 후보인데 내년 골드 글러브 상을 위해.
However, I missed most of the season due to an injury.
그러나 나는 시즌의 대부분을 놓쳤다. 부상으로 인해.
82 million is not fitting for my performance this past season.
8200만은 맞지 않아 지난 시즌 내 활약에 대해.
Huh? What are you talking about?
뭐? 무슨 얘기를 하는 건가요?
If I'm causing a player to be offered less,
플레이어에게 더 적은 금액을 제안하게 한다면
please give that person a fair evaluation.
그 사람을 공정하게 평가해주세요.
Hey, what are you talking about?
무슨 소리 하는 거야?
It's my contract!
내 계약이야!
Let me do what I want.
내가 원하는 것을 하게 해주세요.
We, the Dreams, are a team.
우리 드림스는 하나의 팀입니다.
Hey. Iwata!
여기요. 이와타!
[74 million yen]
[7,400만엔]
Iwata.
이와타.
Iwata!
이와타!
Mr. Kurokawa. You're no longer involved with the Dreams, are you?
쿠로카와 씨. 당신은 더 이상 당신은 드림즈(Dreams)와 관련이 있나요?
Please leave.
떠나주세요.
I'm sorry.
죄송합니다.
For a lot of things.
많은 것들을 위해.
I'll barely forgive you.
나는 거의 당신을 용서할 수 없습니다.
Though, well...
하지만 음...
To make up for my signature,
내 서명을 보충하기 위해
I have a favor to ask.
부탁드릴 게 있어요.
I already know.
나는 이미 알고 있다.
Welcome!
환영!
Welcome.
환영.
Here's your hot towel and water.
여기 뜨거운 수건과 물이 있습니다.
Please call me when you're ready to order.
주문할 준비가 되면 전화해 주세요.
I'm here to apologize today.
오늘은 사과하러 왔습니다.
I made an offer that was far below your estimated worth.
나는 훨씬 낮은 제안을 했다 당신의 추정 가치.
I'm truly sorry.
정말 죄송해요.
No, well...
아니, 음...
Kijima.
키지마.
The Dreams need you.
꿈에는 당신이 필요합니다.
The team's critical financial situation...
팀의 심각한 재정 상황...
meant I could only offer you a meager amount.
내가 당신에게 아주 적은 양만 제안할 수 있다는 뜻이었죠.
It was by no means a notice of dismissal.
결코 해고 통지가 아니었습니다.
My own lack of power is blame.
나 자신의 힘이 부족한 것이 탓이다.
I'm so, truly sorry.
정말 죄송해요.
You've left the team.
당신은 팀을 떠났습니다.
Why go out of your way to apologize?
왜 굳이 사과하러 나가나요?
Because this is the truth.
이것이 진실이기 때문입니다.
Something I couldn't express...
표현할 수 없는 것...
while I worked as GM.
제가 GM으로 일하던 시절.
Do you have any recommendations?
추천 사항이 있나요?
Recommendations, you say...
당신이 말하는 추천은...
Our beef tongue and skirt steak are my picks for the day.
우설과 스커트 스테이크 오늘의 내 선택입니다.
Then I'll have those.
그럼 내가 그걸 가질게.
Sure thing.
확실한 것.
Good evening.
좋은 저녁이에요.
Oh, GM!
아, GM!
I've come with a new offer today.
오늘은 새로운 제안을 가지고 왔습니다.
I told you, I'm no longer...
내가 말했잖아, 난 더 이상...
No, I understand. I hear you.
아니요, 이해합니다. 나는 당신의 말을 듣고 있습니다.
Which is why we offered Iwata your salary as a bonus.
그래서 우리는 이와타에게 당신의 월급을 제안했습니다 보너스로.
But Iwata only had a message for you.
하지만 이와타가 당신에게 전할 메시지는 딱 하나뿐이었습니다.
He said, "I still want to catch Kijima's pitches."
그는 말했다, "아직도 키지마의 공을 잡고 싶어요."
He asked me to bring you back.
그는 나에게 당신을 다시 데려오라고 요청했습니다.
Iwata did?
이와타는 그랬나요?
Yes.
예.
Don't worry.
걱정하지 마세요.
I'm ready to catch your pitches next season.
다음 시즌에 여러분의 투구를 따라잡을 준비가 되었습니다.
Mr. Kijima...
키지마 씨...
Can I go grab a pen?
펜을 가지러 갈 수 있을까요?
Of course.
물론.
GM!
GM!
We did it!
우리가 해냈어!
GM?
GM?
We didn't lose a single player.
우리는 단 한 명의 선수도 잃지 않았습니다.
Yup!
예!
Everyone has been signed on!
모두가 로그인했습니다!
Alright! I'm treating today!
괜찮은! 오늘 진료 중이에요!
Don't get cocky just because your family is rich.
자만하지 마세요 단지 당신의 가족이 부자이기 때문입니다.
But today's a special occasion.
하지만 오늘은 특별한 날이에요.
People will keep saying you got in through connections.
사람들은 계속 말하겠지 당신은 인맥을 통해 들어왔습니다.
- You're the only one who harps on that! - Alright...
- 그걸 하프로 부르는 사람은 너뿐이야! - 알겠습니다...
Let's give it our all this winter,
이번 겨울 내내 최선을 다하자
and make our next season a success!
다음 시즌도 성공하게 해주세요!
Cheers!
건배!
- Cheers!
- 건배!
Good work.
잘했어요.
Likewise, sir.
마찬가지로요, 선생님.
What? Did you want to treat us that badly?
무엇? 우리를 그렇게 나쁘게 대하고 싶었나요?
No, that's not it.
아니요, 그게 아닙니다.
But the GM isn't...
하지만 GM은 그렇지 않습니다...
Sorry.
죄송합니다.
We've lost our key player, haven't we?
우리는 핵심 선수를 잃었습니다. 그렇죠?
On the GM's last day,
GM의 마지막 날,
I received the handover documents he made.
나는 그가 작성한 인수인계 서류를 받았습니다.
There were so many documents.
문서가 너무 많았어요.
He must have spent hundreds of hours researching everything about the Dreams.
그는 수백 시간을 보냈을 것입니다 꿈에 관한 모든 것을 조사하고 있습니다.
He said he had no attachment to the team.
그는 팀에 대한 애착이 없다고 말했습니다.
But I don't believe him for a second.
하지만 나는 잠시도 그를 믿지 않습니다.
I think my brother...
내 생각엔 내 동생이...
is afraid of having something important to him.
갖는 것을 두려워한다 그에게 중요한 것.
Afraid?
두려워하는?
He doesn't want to suffer loss ever again.
그는 다시는 손실을 겪고 싶지 않습니다.
That's why he doesn't save anyone's contact info.
그래서 그 사람은 저장을 안 하는 거고 누군가의 연락처 정보.
When I got hurt,
내가 다쳤을 때,
my brother lost his family, too.
내 동생도 가족을 잃었어요.
That's enough!
그거면 충분해요!
What happened to Akito is not your fault.
아키토에게 일어난 일은 당신의 잘못이 아닙니다.
If I had been a bit more perceptive...
내가 좀 더 예민했더라면...
If I hadn't said those things, none of this would've happened!
내가 그런 말을 하지 않았다면, 이런 일은 일어나지 않았을 거야!
Enough with the "ifs" and the self-blame!
"ifs"와 자책은 이제 그만!
Are we not allowed to move on?
계속 진행하면 안 되나요?
Well, are we?
글쎄요?
Ouch.
아야.
- Ouch. - Sawako?
- 아야. - 사와코?
Sawako! Sawako!
사와코! 사와코!
Hey.
여기요.
Are you okay?
괜찮으세요?
Sawako!
사와코!
My brother...
내 동생...
continued to blame himself.
계속해서 자신을 비난했습니다.
He felt responsible for everything.
그는 모든 것에 책임감을 느꼈습니다.
Unable to focus on work anymore,
더 이상 업무에 집중할 수 없습니다.
he was transferred to a hockey team on the verge of disbanding.
그는 하키팀으로 이적했어요 해체 직전.
My brother eventually filed his divorce,
내 동생은 결국 이혼 소송을 제기했고,
and began working solely for my sake.
오직 나를 위해서 일하기 시작했습니다.
Though he led that hockey team to victory,
비록 그가 그 하키 팀을 승리로 이끌었지만,
they ultimately disbanded after a year.
그들은 결국 1년 만에 해체됐다.
Afterwards, he drifted aimlessly from sport to sport.
그 후 그는 목적 없이 표류했다. 스포츠에서 스포츠로.
No one protected him.
아무도 그를 보호하지 않았습니다.
I think my brother is beginning to care about the Dreams.
내 생각엔 형이 꿈에 관심을 갖기 시작했습니다.
So...
그럼...
He's blaming himself again.
그는 또 자신을 비난하고 있습니다.
What?
무엇?
To quote the GM directly,
GM의 말을 직접 인용하려면,
he said these negotiations hurt the players,
그는 이 협상이 선수들에게 상처를 준다고 말했어요
and destroyed the team.
그리고 팀을 무너뜨렸습니다.
- That doesn't sit right with me. - Huh?
- 그건 나랑 안 맞는 것 같아. - 뭐?
We ought to do the protecting, too.
우리도 보호해야 합니다.
Right?
오른쪽?
Maybe it's not too late.
어쩌면 너무 늦지 않았을 수도 있습니다.
Let's protect the GM, together.
GM을 함께 보호합시다.
Yes, ma'am!
네, 부인!
I've arranged this press conference today
오늘 기자회견을 준비했어요
to explain our decision in hiring our GM's brother.
우리의 결정을 설명하기 위해 우리 GM의 동생을 고용하는데 있어서요.
First, we only discovered they were brothers after the interview.
먼저, 우리는 그들이 형제라는 것을 알게 되었습니다. 인터뷰 후.
The GM gave his brother the lowest score.
GM은 그의 동생에게 가장 낮은 점수를 주었습니다.
While myself and Analytics Director Inamura, gave him full marks.
저와 분석 책임자인 Inamura는 그에게 만점을 주었다.
Though we hired the applicant with the highest total score,
지원자를 고용했지만 총점이 가장 높은
we understand this caused a misunderstanding.
우리는 이것이 오해를 야기했다는 것을 이해합니다.
However, Akito Sakurazaki is actually...
하지만 사쿠라자키 아키토는 사실...
What was that press conference?
그 기자회견은 뭐였나요?
It was a means to restore the team's credibility.
수단이었어 팀의 신뢰를 회복하기 위해.
What?
무엇?
Our upcoming announcement of the GM's resignation would have sufficed.
우리의 다가오는 발표 GM의 사임이면 충분했을 것입니다.
It was more important to reveal the truth.
진실을 밝히는 것이 더 중요했습니다.
Our negotiations with Iwata have also come to a close.
이와타와의 협상 또한 가까워졌습니다.
Is there any reason to fire the GM now?
지금 GM을 해고할 이유가 있나요?
Yes?
예?
Breaking news.
속보.
Akito's suspicions have been completely cleared.
아키토의 의심 완전히 지워졌습니다.
[Dreams Analyst was the famed "Robinson"!]
[드림즈 분석가는 그 유명한 "로빈슨"이었습니다!]
Did you suddenly become a reporter?
갑자기 기자가 된 건가요?
A smile would do, you know.
미소만 지으면 됩니다.
No more taking all the blame yourself.
더 이상 모든 책임을 스스로 떠맡지 마세요.
Please come back to the Dreams.
드림즈로 돌아와주세요.
My salary has already been guaranteed.
내 월급은 이미 보장됐어요.
Why should I return to a last-place team now?
왜 지금 꼴찌팀으로 돌아가야 하는가?
Again with the cold attitude.
또 차가운 태도로.
I'm sure you already know why.
나는 당신이 이미 그 이유를 알고 있다고 확신합니다.
The Dreams were never allowed to be dreamers.
꿈은 결코 몽상가가 되는 것이 허용되지 않았습니다.
No one protected the team, after all.
결국 아무도 팀을 보호하지 못했습니다.
But now, things are different.
하지만 지금은 상황이 다릅니다.
The Dreams have you.
꿈에는 당신이 있습니다.
Let's protect the team, together.
함께 팀을 보호합시다.
We're not alone.
우리는 혼자가 아닙니다.
Mr. Inamura joined me at the press conference.
이나무라 씨가 합류했습니다 기자회견에서.
This article was written by PR Director Suzumori.
이 글은 작성되었습니다 홍보 이사 스즈모리.
Even Miyahara worked his butt off.
Miyahara조차도 엉덩이를 풀었습니다.
Akito cleared his name with his own efforts.
아키토는 자신의 노력으로 자신의 이름을 지웠습니다.
President Negishi once told me...
네기시 사장이 나에게 말한 적이 있다...
that in an organization, you can't stick to your beliefs.
그건 조직에서, 당신은 당신의 신념을 고수할 수 없습니다.
But I believe with the right people, it's entirely possible.
하지만 나는 올바른 사람들과 함께 있다고 믿습니다. 그것은 전적으로 가능합니다.
President Makita.
마키타 회장.
I sent our player's into turmoil.
나는 우리 선수들을 혼란에 빠뜨렸다.
So if I am to return,
그래서 내가 돌아오려면
I wish to go back with a fight.
나는 싸움으로 돌아가고 싶다.
Will you help me?
나를 도와주실 건가요?
Of course!
물론!
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
What can I do for you?
제가 당신을 위해 무엇을 도와드릴까요?
Isami.
이사미.
Yes.
예.
Here's a question.
여기에 질문이 있습니다.
Is it difficult to have your subordinate's servants carry your packages?
부하 직원을 갖는 것이 어렵습니까? 하인들이 당신의 짐을 들고 다니나요?
Yes or no?
예 아니면 아니오?
No!
아니요!
In that case...
그렇다면...
What the hell is going on here?
도대체 무슨 일이 일어나고 있는 걸까요?
A servant's negligence has the packages catching fire,
하인의 과실 패키지에 불이 붙었습니다.
and now my house is burning down!
그런데 지금 내 집이 불타고 있어요!
[Can the Dreams not afford their GM?]
[드림즈는 GM을 감당할 여유가 없나요?]
[The Yaoshima Group, in dire straits?]
[야오시마 그룹, 위기에 빠졌나?]
Sir.
선생님.
These are all false reports.
이것들은 모두 거짓 보고입니다.
False reports?
거짓 보고?
Who could have manipulated all this information?
누가 조작했을까 이 정보가 다요?
I told you, didn't I?
내가 말했지, 그렇지?
I have no need for empty promises of mochi.
떡에 대한 공허한 약속은 필요 없습니다.
Yet our stock is plummeting,
그런데 우리 주식이 폭락하고 있어요
and my entire Group is suffering huge losses!
내 그룹 전체가 막대한 손실을 입고 있습니다!
How do you explain that?
그걸 어떻게 설명하나요?
Who did this!
누가 그랬어!
I will deal with it immediately.
즉시 처리하겠습니다.
You'd better.
차라리.
You have until day's end.
오늘이 끝날 때까지 시간이 있습니다.
Hurry up!
서둘러요!
Yes, sir.
네, 선생님.
Now, now, now, now.
지금, 지금, 지금, 지금.
Relax.
안심하다.
Hang in there, yeah?
조금만 참아, 응?
At least until I take over.
적어도 내가 물려받기 전까지는요.
Hey.
여기요.
Why are you dawdling?
왜 꾸물거리고 있나요?
You've got a fire to put out. Go on.
당신은 꺼야 할 불이 있습니다. 계속하세요.
Hurry up!
서둘러요!
I can't think of anyone else who could spread such an article.
다른 사람은 생각이 안 나 누가 이런 기사를 퍼뜨릴 수 있겠는가.
What do you think you're doing?
지금 뭐하고 있는 것 같나요?
I told you I'd guarantee your salary!
내가 네 월급을 보장해 주겠다고 했잖아!
It seems the reporter misunderstood my statement regarding "budget cuts".
기자가 오해한거 같네요 "예산 삭감"에 관한 나의 진술.
Enough fooling around.
장난치는 것만으로도 충분합니다.
Do you realize how much our shareholders lost because of your shallow prank?
우리 주주들이 얼마나 많은 손실을 입었는지 아시나요? 너의 천박한 장난 때문에?
I wouldn't know. 30 percent?
나는 모른다. 30퍼센트?
That is not funny.
그거 재미없잖아.
Stocks are only down 9%.
주식은 9%만 하락했다.
The players suffered a 30% cut.
선수들은 30% 삭감을 겪었다.
Watch your mouth!
입 조심해!
I'll withdraw your dismissal as GM,
GM 해임을 철회하겠습니다
so quickly retract the article.
그러니 빨리 기사를 철회하세요.
My brother's allegedly "suspicious" hire,
내 동생의 "의심스러운" 고용인,
and our salary negotiation issues have all been resolved.
연봉협상 문제도 그렇고 모두 해결되었습니다.
Regardless of what you say,
당신이 무슨 말을 하든,
I no longer have any reason to quit as GM.
더 이상 GM직을 그만둘 이유가 없습니다.
Then what is it you want?
그렇다면 당신이 원하는 것은 무엇입니까?
If you're so concerned about the 9% drop,
9% 하락이 그렇게 걱정된다면,
then raise our total salary budget.
그런 다음 총 급여 예산을 늘리십시오.
Those cuts are why the group looks financially unstable.
그 상처 때문에 그룹이 재정적으로 불안정해 보입니다.
Fine, I'll give you that paltry sum. Now retract the article!
좋아요, 그 보잘것없는 액수를 드리겠습니다. 이제 기사를 철회하세요!
What did you just say?
방금 뭐라고 했어?
Huh?
뭐?
Do you realize your "paltry sum"...
당신의 "미미한 액수"를 알고 계십니까...
had the staff and players at each other's necks?
스태프도 있고 선수도 있었고 서로 목에?
I suggest you give that some thought.
나는 당신이 그것에 대해 좀 생각해 볼 것을 제안합니다.
Why do you refuse to obey me?
왜 나에게 순종하기를 거부합니까?
Will obeying orders change anything?
명령에 순종하면 변화가 있을까요?
In my experience, it never does.
내 경험상 절대 그렇지 않습니다.
Do your experiences prove me wrong?
당신의 경험이 내가 틀렸다는 것을 증명합니까?
[Fukumoto]
[후쿠모토]
So, the GM.
그러니까 GM.
What happened to him?
그에게 무슨 일이 일어났나요?
I'll fill you in later.
나중에 채워드리겠습니다.
We have negotiations to redo.
우리는 다시 협상을 해야 합니다.
Huh?
뭐?
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
Good afternoon.
좋은 오후에요.
- Good afternoon.
- 좋은 오후에요.
Have a seat.
앉으세요.
Your contract has been modified.
귀하의 계약이 수정되었습니다.
Please look over our revisions.
우리의 개정판을 살펴보시기 바랍니다.
[34.5 million yen]
[3,450만엔]
What?
무엇?
It's a 15% increase.
15% 증가입니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
[12 million yen]
[1,200만엔]
We recognize it's a small increase, but...
소폭의 증가인 것으로 알고 있지만...
Oh, no. It helps a lot.
안 돼. 많은 도움이 됩니다.
But why?
그런데 왜?
Mr. Sakurazaki went and negotiated with the owner.
사쿠라자키 씨가 가서 교섭을 했습니다. 주인과 함께.
He wanted the players' true values to be recognized.
그는 선수들의 진정한 가치를 원했다 인식되는 것.
- The GM did? - Yes!
- GM이 그랬나요? - 예!
Thank you very much.
매우 감사합니다.
Here's to another year!
또 다른 해가 왔습니다!
- The pleasure's mine. - Thank you.
- 기쁨은 나의 것입니다. - 감사합니다.
Alright!
괜찮은!
[Signature - Yuki Kijima]
[시그니처 - 키지마 유키]
Hey, Kijima!
안녕, 키지마!
Oh, Iwata!
아, 이와타!
Listen...
들어봐...
It didn't work at all.
전혀 작동하지 않았습니다.
Huh?
뭐?
My plan to threaten staff for big bucks.
큰 돈을 받고 직원을 위협할 계획이에요.
You're a real menace, you know that?
당신은 정말 위협적인 사람이에요, 그거 알아요?
Instead, I'm going to make a fortune winning the series next season.
대신에 돈 많이 벌겠다 다음 시즌 시리즈 우승.
You in?
당신은?
Yeah...
응...
You've got a deal!
당신은 거래를했습니다!
Woah there!
와 거기!
Here he comes!
여기 그가 온다!
- Go, go, go! - You weigh nothing.
- 가, 가, 가! - 몸무게는 없어요.
Count me in for next season!
다음 시즌에도 저를 참여시켜주세요!
Alright!
괜찮은!
Get him!
그를 잡아!
Stop it!
그만해요!
I don't have my shoes today!
오늘은 신발이 없어요!
Don't get antsy, folks.
짜증내지 마세요 여러분.
- We're just early. - Right, right.
- 우리는 아직 이른 것 같아요. - 그렇죠, 그렇죠.
He's here, he's here!
그가 여기 있어요, 그가 여기 있어요!
And he turned the corner.
그리고 그는 모퉁이를 돌았습니다.
Hey!
여기요!
Never mind, here he comes!
신경쓰지 마세요. 그가 옵니다!
Get ready! Everyone ready?
준비하세요! 다들 준비됐나요?
Ready?
준비가 된?
Welcome back!
돌아온 것을 환영합니다!
Our GM has returned!
우리 GM이 돌아왔습니다!
GM.
GM.
And if I may add, I went and bought the cake.
그리고 덧붙이자면, 나는 가서 케이크를 샀다.
Huh?
뭐?
Really? That's it?
정말? 그게 다야?
Well, hey. At least he blew out his candles.
글쎄요. 적어도 그는 촛불을 불었다.
He's going to shut himself in his room again.
그는 다시 자기 방에 틀어박혀 있을 것이다.
He's going to be immersed in work again.
그는 다시 일에 몰두하게 될 것이다.
But we bought a cake! He's so cold-hearted.
하지만 우리는 케이크를 샀어요! 그 사람은 너무 냉정해요.
I'm sorry about him.
그 사람에 대해서는 미안해요.
If you're sorry, finish the cake in his stead!
미안하다면, 그 사람 대신 케이크를 완성해 줘!
That's right!
좋아요!
Eat the whole thing!
다 먹어라!
- The whole cake? - Yeah, yeah.
- 케이크 전체요? - 응, 응.
Come in.
들어오세요.
Excuse me.
실례합니다.
GM.
GM.
We'll be holding a welcome-back party for you tonight.
우리는 개최할 것이다 오늘 밤 당신을 위한 환영 파티입니다.
I won't be there.
나는 거기에 없을 것이다.
But you're the guest of honor.
하지만 당신은 영예로운 손님입니다.
Fine.
괜찮은.
President Makita.
마키타 회장.
Yes.
예.
I am here today thanks to all of you.
여러분 덕분에 제가 오늘 이 자리에 섰습니다.
Please tell them I'm grateful.
그들에게 고맙다고 전해주세요.
Okay.
좋아요.
I will definitely tell them.
나는 그들에게 확실히 말할 것입니다.
You should have started with that.
그것부터 시작했어야 했어요.
Actually, why not tell them yourself?
사실, 그들에게 직접 말해 보는 것은 어떨까요?
I'll think about it.
생각해 볼게요.
Then if you'll excuse me.
그럼 실례하겠습니다.
Our player roster for the season has finally been solidified.
이번 시즌 선수 명단 드디어 굳어졌습니다.
What a harrowing negotiation period.
참으로 괴로운 협상 기간이었습니다.
Now we can fully prepare for camp.
이제 우리는 캠프를 완벽하게 준비할 수 있습니다.
Alright!
괜찮은!
I will announce our potential camping sites.
가능한 캠핑장을 알려드리겠습니다.
I'm betting on Okinawa.
저는 오키나와에 베팅하겠습니다.
[Mom]
[엄마]
Yes, what is it?
응, 그게 뭐야?
Huh?
뭐?
What do you mean?
무슨 뜻이에요?
Why does Dad have to fix someone else's roof?
왜 아빠는 남의 지붕을 고쳐줘야 하나요?
Oh, I see.
알겠어요.
Why do you only call in dire situations?
왜 어려운 상황에만 전화하는 걸까요?
Give me a break!
나에게 휴식을 주세요!
Okay, okay. I'll wire you the money.
알았어, 알았어. 돈을 송금해 드리겠습니다.
Bye.
안녕.
[Ryuta]
[류타]
Did you hear that?
그거 들었어?
- Don't be stupid. - No, seriously. Did you?
- 바보같은 소리 하지 마세요. - 아뇨, ​​진심이에요. 그랬나요?
There's no way I'd say it first.
내가 먼저 말할 방법은 없어.
Unbelievable.
믿을 수 없는.
That's not fair. I said it first, didn't I?
그건 불공평해요. 내가 먼저 말했지, 그렇지?
Hey, we've been waiting for you.
안녕하세요, 우리는 당신을 기다리고 있었습니다.
Sorry to keep you waiting.
기다리게 해서 죄송합니다.
Here, have a drink.
자, 한잔 드세요.
You're wasted.
당신은 낭비입니다.
Thank you.
감사합니다.
- Cheers!
- 건배!
I heard you're interested in medicine.
당신이 의학에 관심이 있다고 들었어요.
My uncle's a medical man himself. I'll introduce you next time.
우리 삼촌도 의료인이에요. 다음에 소개할게요.
Yes?
예?
Oh, please do.
아, 그렇게 해주세요.
But why medicine? Is someone in your family a doctor?
그런데 왜 약인가? 가족 중에 의사가 있나요?
No. Not exactly.
아니요. 정확히는 아닙니다.
Hey. His dad is unemployed.
여기요. 그의 아버지는 실업자입니다.
I just told you.
방금 말했어요.
Shut up!
입 다물어!
Oh, my apologies.
아, 죄송해요.
But until a while ago,
하지만 얼마 전까지만 해도
he used to do work changing light bulbs.
그는 전구를 바꾸는 일을 하곤 했어요.
But seriously, what kind of job is that?
그런데 진지하게, 그게 무슨 직업인가요?
- Changing light bulbs? - I wouldn't know.
- 전구를 바꾸나요? - 난 모르겠어.
- Never seen that before. - Never even heard of it!
- 그런 건 본 적이 없어요. - 들어본 적도 없어요!
Anyway, this guy was done in by his own subordinate.
어쨌든 이 사람은 끝났어 자신의 부하에 의해.
He dropped our stocks by 9%.
그는 우리 주식을 9% 하락시켰습니다.
Nine percent!
9퍼센트!
Just between you and me, this father and son?
너와 나 사이에만, 이 아버지와 아들?
They're lacking here.
여기에는 부족해요.
Don't tell them though. It's our secret!
하지만 그들에게 말하지 마세요. 그것은 우리의 비밀입니다!
So what? That was your fault?
그래서 뭐? 그게 당신 잘못이었나요?
Come on, man. I lost money too.
어서, 친구. 나도 돈을 잃었다.
Alright, alright, alright.
알았어, 알았어, 알았어.
Isami said he'd pay up, yeah?
이사미가 돈을 낸다고 했죠?
- Oh, I see. - That's right.
- 알겠어요. - 좋아요.
It'll work out.
잘 될 거예요.
Let's arm wrestle.
팔씨름을 하자.
You versus me.
당신 대 나.
Huh?
뭐?
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
You think you can beat me in arm wrestling?
팔씨름으로 나를 이길 수 있을 것 같아?
Don't get cocky.
자만하지 마십시오.
Come on.
어서 해봐요.
Burning with rivalry against me?
나에 대한 경쟁심이 불타오르고 있나요?
Don't get ahead of yourself!
너무 앞서가지 마세요!
I'll be the referee.
내가 심판이 될게요.
This'll be a piece of cake.
이건 아주 쉬운 일이 될 거예요.
Hey look.
이봐.
The perfect arena.
완벽한 경기장.
Hold that for me.
저한테 맡겨주세요.
Alright, bring it.
알았어, 가져와.
Ready, go!
준비됐어요!
Go, go!
가, 가!
What?
무엇?
Is that all you've got?
당신이 가진 전부인가요?
What's wrong?
무슨 일이야?
- Hey, come on. - What's wrong? What's wrong?
- 이봐, 어서. - 무슨 일이야? 무슨 일이야?
Let me have it.
내가 갖게 해줘.
You're going to lose!
당신은 잃을 것입니다!
No way.
안 돼요.
He's so weak!
그는 너무 약해요!
- Seriously? - Lame!
- 진지하게? - 절뚝거리는!
Alright! It's over!
괜찮은! 끝났습니다!
Heave-ho!
헤비호!
Hey!
여기요!
Wait a minute!
잠깐 기다려요!
Time, time! Give me a second!
시간, 시간! 잠시만 기다려주세요!
Damn it!
젠장!
Hey, let go!
이봐, 놔!
Let go of me!
날 놔줘!
You're weak because you've never struggled a damn day in your life!
당신은 한 번도 어려움을 겪어본 적이 없기 때문에 약합니다. 네 인생의 빌어먹을 하루!
Quit disrespecting my father.
아버지를 무시하지 마세요.
He's also your uncle!
그 사람도 네 삼촌이야!